[{"answer": "You're back.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Can you hear me?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "I think it was a week or two, as I remember.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "How long was it before he finally told you?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I'm almost 74.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Where do you feel you get the strength to be like this?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I'm serious.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "Oh, my goodness, my husband telling me that he thought we should adopt.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "If I could replay a moment for you now, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Oh, that's great.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Valerie, how -- finally, how would you like to be remembered?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, because in Boston, Mohammad Atta and nine other al Qaeda hijacked two planes back in 9/11.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "The question is what can destroy an airplane.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Who needs to have a knife in mid-air anyway?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Yes, you actually can kill and bring down a plane with a knife.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Mary Schiavo, am I missing something?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "The threat is -- because they will be shot dead by federal air marshals or, you know --", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Just to clarify, there is a federal marshal aboard every single domestic flight in America, is there?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Because look -- look at it from the TSA's point of view, which is there is a real threat of bombs.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "How do you know they are going to shoot them dead if they are not an board?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Because the level of security is just night and day from before 9/11 to today.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Why are you so confident it's not going to happen?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Am I missing something?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Well, you are probably not surprised to hear, we are not for sexual abuse.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Lino, what do people feel about that down there?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "(inaudible) fact.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "And what do you think may happen here?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Assault weapons ban, there is very little support for assault weapons.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "What about an assault weapons ban?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Look, this is about something very holy.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "When the new Pope is in play, what should they be thinking to do?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "President Obama knows this.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "What is the way through this impasse, particularly in getting a proper budget deal done, proper debt deal done, making sure the America is the focal point of how we move forward here?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Well, a bit of a disclosure.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Has Lance Armstrong got that kind of chance, do you think?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130312pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "But is it a possibility?", "qSentId": 654}]